字幕翻译/压制：旋火
视频来源：youtu.be/wSge0I7pwFI
原视频发布日期：20200422
原作者名：SpaceX
时间索引：
03:28 节目正式开始
14:46 火箭发射倒计时15秒
16:05 火箭超音速&Max-Q
17:40 一级发动机关机&一二级分离&二级点火
18:15 整流罩分离
21:52 一级再入点火
23:22 一级着陆点火
24:15 二级发动机关机
30:09 星箭分离
[Music]
[音乐]
发射综合体39A
地球，佛罗里达，肯尼迪航天中心
Good afternoon it is Wednesday April 22nd
下午好 现在是4月22日周三
and you are looking at a live view of Falcon 9
你正在观看猎鹰9号的直播
as it awaits it's the 3:31 p.m. Eastern Time launched
正在等待于美国东部时间15:31
星链
二级煤油加注
二级液氧加注
from Pad 39A at Kennedy Space Center in Florida.
从佛罗里达肯尼迪航天中心39A发射台进行发射
Hello from SpaceX headquarters in Hawthorne California.
你好 我在加州霍桑的SpaceX公司总部
My name is Lauren Lyons and I'm an engineer on the Starlink team here at SpaceX
我是Lauren Lyons SpaceX星链团队的工程师
and you are watching a live webcast for our seventh Starlink mission and our seventh mission this year.
而你正在看我们第七次星链任务 也是今年第七次任务的直播
To date we've launched over 360 Starlink satellites to orbit and
迄今为止 我们已经发射了超过360颗星链卫星入轨
as a reminder Starlink is a constellation of satellites
需要指出的是 Starlink是一个卫星星座
that can provide high speed low latency internet across the globe particularly in remote areas
可在全球范围内提供高速低延迟互联网 特别是偏远地区
where connectivity is limited or completely unavailable.
这些偏远地区的互联网要么受限要么完全不可用
The Falcon 9 booster that you see on your screen will be plot flying today for the fourth time.
你屏幕上看到的猎鹰9号一级火箭将在今天计划进行第四次发射
It previously supported crew dragons first demonstration mission to the International Space Station
它之前支持了载人龙飞船第一次演示任务的发射到国际空间站
back in March of 2019.
那时是在2019年3月份
The launch of the RADARSAT constellation mission in June 2019
在2019年6月发射了RADARSAT(雷达卫星)星座任务
and the January 2020 launch of the Starlink mission.
还有2020年1月发射的星链任务
Just like our first stages we are also starting to reuse our fairings.
就像我们重复使用一级火箭一样 我们也开始重复使用整流罩
Today we are flying a reuse fairing which previously flew on the AMOS-17 mission last year.
今天猎鹰9号的发射将会重复使用去年AMOS-17任务的整流罩
I mentioned that this booster flew on crew dragons first demonstration mission to the space station
我提到过这个一级火箭它发射过载人龙飞船的第一次演示任务到国际空间站
and if you follow SpaceX you know the date for our second demo mission is May 27th.
如果你一直在关注SpaceX 你会知道第二次演示任务是在5月27日
It'll be a historic mission launching
这将是一个历史性的发射任务
American astronauts from US soil to the International Space Station for the first time since 2011
是自2011年以来首次从美国本土发射美国宇航员到国际空间站
and we'll touch on that more later on in the broadcast.
我们在稍后的直播中会提到
If for any reason there is a hold on the countdown today
如果由于某种原因今天的倒计时停止了
we do have a backup launch window opportunity tomorrow at 3:16 p.m. East.
还有一个备用发射窗口时间在明天东部时间的15:16
So with that all systems are go for an on-time liftoff this evening
那么 这个傍晚所有的系统都准备就绪可以及时发射
Now you may recall during our last Starlink mission.
你现在也许还能回想起上次星链任务
There was an early engine shutdown on Falcon 9's first stage during ascent.
在上升段 猎鹰9号的一级火箭有一个发动机过早地停机了
The Falcon 9 booster safely completed its mission
猎鹰9号的一级火箭安全地完成了它的使命
as it was designed to in the event of an engine shutdown
因为设计上它允许有一台发动机关机的事件发生
and delivered the satellites to their intended orbit.
并把卫星交付到它们的预定轨道
Since then our engineers determined that the issue stemmed from a small amount of isopropyl alcohol
在那之后我们的工程师确定问题源于少量的异丙醇
which is a cleaning fluid that became trapped inside of a sensor dead leg
这是一种液体清洁剂留在了一个传感器的死角里
or an area where it couldn't flow through and then ignited.
然后被点燃
We did not perform that cleaning process on the rocket supporting today's mission
今天的任务中 我们没有采用同样的清洗过程
and all nine Merlin engines which were test fired on the pad just last week
而上周9个梅林发动机都在发射台进行了点火测试
are looking healthy ahead of flight.
在发射前看来状态很好
Prior to today's launch the vehicle was housed in our hangar at Launch Complex 39A
在今天的发射前 火箭存储在LC 39A的SpaceX机库里
until about 24 hours ago
直到大约24小时前
when the rocket along with the Starlink payload was rolled out to the pad and raised vertical.
当火箭和有效载荷星链一起转运到发射台并被起竖
The bottom two-thirds of the vehicle that you can see there that is the first stage.
火箭下部三分之二的部分是一级火箭
You can actually see the soot markings left over from its last flight.
实际上 你可以看到它上一次飞行遗留的烟灰
The first stage is what accelerates the vehicle through the Earth's atmosphere to the edge of space
一级火箭帮助有效载荷穿过大气层并到达太空的边界
with the help of nine Merlin engines at the base of the rocket.
这段时间是火箭底部的9台梅林发动机在帮忙
Today we'll be attempting to
今天 我们将尝试
这里只是指第四次回收B1051这枚火箭，而非指第四次在无人船上回收这枚火箭
B1051进行了一次陆上返场回收，三次无人船回收
recover the first stage for the fourth time on our drone ship Of Course I Still Love You
会在无人船 当然我还是爱你 上第四次回收这枚一级火箭
which you can see there
你可以看到它在那儿
and it's currently stationed about 350 nautical miles northeast off the Cape.
在卡角东北部大概350海里的位置
Above the first stage is the second stage
一级上面是二级
which has a single single Merlin Vacuum or M-Vac engine
二级只有一个真空梅林或者说M-Vac发动机
which ignites after the first stage separates.
会在一级分离后点火
The second stage is what will carry the Starlink satellites into an elliptical orbit above the Earth's surface
二级将会把星链卫星送入地球表面上的椭圆轨道
From there they'll use their propulsion systems to move up to their operational altitude of 550 km.
在那个轨道上 它们会使用自己的推进系统抬升至550km的目标轨道
Falcon 9 began loading propellants at t-minus 35 minutes
猎鹰9号会在倒计时35分钟的时候开始加注推进剂
and as a reminder we use a rocket grade kerosene or RP1 as our fuel
需要指出的是 猎鹰9号使用航天级别的煤油或者说RP1作为燃料
and super chilled liquid oxygen or LOX as our oxidizer to power the Falcon 9.
以及过冷却的液氧或者说LOX作为氧化剂
Currently RP1 and LOX are nearly fully loaded on both stages
目前两个分级上RP1和LOX基本都加满了
and LOX will continue to be topped up until the last minute of the countdown.
而LOX将持续加满直到倒计时的最后一分钟
The stack of 60 Starlink satellites is safely enclosed inside of the 17 foot diameter payload fairing
60颗星链卫星的堆栈已经安全地装入5.2m直径的整流罩中
which you can see there that pointed cone at the very top of the rocket.
你可以火箭的顶部有着尖尖的鼻锥
This protects the satellites from aerothermal heating aerodynamic loads and contamination during ascent.
有了这层保护 卫星在火箭上升段就不会受到气动热 气动负载还有空气污染的影响
Once we reach the vacuum of space we will jettison the fairing
一旦到达太空的真空环境下 火箭将抛弃整流罩
as the second stage continues on its journey to orbit
与此同时二级继续它的入轨的过程
(一级)发动机预冷
We won't be attempting to catch the fairing hats and our Nets today
今天我们不会尝试用网回收整流罩
as our boat and fairing software are undergoing upgrades.
因为我们的船和整流罩的软件正在进行升级
But weather permitting we will try to recover them from the water.
但是 天气允许的话 我们会尝试从水中回收它们
Using our recovery ships Ms. Tree and Ms. Chief.
使用我们的回收船 Tree女士和Chief女士
And there's a live view from one of those ships.
这个则是其中一艘船的实时画面
So as you can see the water is looking a little rough so stay tuned.
你可以看到海况有点不太好 那么敬请留意吧
Now if you've been tracking the lead up to today's launch,
现在 如果你之前关注过我们的发射
you know that the weather has been a watch item.
你知道 天气一直以来都是一个需要注意的事项
For the last several days with tornado warnings moving through the area,
在过去的数天 这附近的区域受到过龙卷风警告
our rocket and payload however were in the hangar as the storm passed
但是在风暴来临时 我们的火箭和有效载荷都在机库里
so we didn't see any adverse impacts as a result of that weather.
所以我们没看到任何天气带来的负面影响
And today it's looking like a beautiful day for a launch
而今天看来是一个适合发射的天气
so with that the vehicles, satellites, weather and range are all looking good for an on-time liftoff
所以火箭 卫星 天气还有区域控制都适合及时起飞
just a few minutes from now.
现在离发射还差几分钟了
As I mentioned at the top of the webcast SpaceX and NASA are now targeting May 27
我在直播开头说过SpaceX和NASA计划在5月27日
for Falcon 9 launch of crew dragons second demonstration mission or Demo-2 as we like to call it.
用猎鹰9号发射载人龙第二次演示任务 或者说Demo-2任务
This will be the first time that a commercially built spacecraft will launch people to the space station
这将是首个商业制造的航天器 将会把人们运往国际空间站
and the first time in nearly ten years that the US has launched astronauts into space from US soil.
而且是近十年以来第一次美国从本土发射宇航员进入太空
Demo-2 is an end-to-end flight test from launch to docking to splashdown
Demo-2是一个全流程发射测试 从发射到对接到溅落
and it is the final major milestone for SpaceX is human space flight system
它会是SpaceX载人航天系统的最后一个重要里程碑
to be certified for NASA for operational crewed missions to and from the International Space Station.
由NASA认证 可以运作往返国际空间站的任务
Bob Behnken and Doug Hurley will be the first two NASA astronauts to fly aboard crew dragon
Bob Behnken和Doug Hurley将会是最初乘坐载人龙飞船的两名NASA宇航员
after completing countless hours of training both at SpaceX and at NASA's training facilities.
他们在这之前在SpaceX和NASA的训练设施中进行了无数小时的训练
Both the spacecraft and the launch vehicle are at the Cape and undergoing preparations
航天器和火箭都在卡角进行准备工作
and as you may have seen on social Falcon 9 is getting a special paint job for the Demo-2 mission.
正如你在社交媒体上看到的那样 猎鹰9号会因为Demo-2任务得到一个特殊涂装
That's right NASA has brought back the famous worm logo
没错 NASA带回了著名的蠕虫标志
as you can see the logo painted on the Demo-2 Falcon 9 booster in this picture
你可以在这张图片中看到这个标志涂装在猎鹰9号Demo-2任务的一级火箭上
The worm was brought back
这个蠕虫标志的回归
to mark the return of human spaceflight on American Rockets from American soil with the Demo-2 mission.
是为了纪念使用美国火箭在美国本土再度进行载人航天发射的Demo-2任务
Once Demo-2 is complete and the SpaceX and NASA teams have reviewed all the data for certification,
一旦Demo-2完成了 而SpaceX和NASA的团队审查完所有需要认证的数据后
JAXA = 日本宇宙航空研究开发机构
NASA astronauts Victor Glover, Mike Hopkins, Shannon Walker and JAXA astronauts Soichi Noguchi
NASA宇航员Victor Glover, Mike Hopkins, Shannon Walker还有JAXA宇航员野口聪一
服务塔架分离
have been assigned to fly on dragons first six-month operational mission
已经分配给了龙飞船第一次6个月长度的运营任务
which we are calling Crew-1 and are targeting for later this year.
我们称之为Crew-1 并于今年晚些时候的计划发射
So we are just currently just over four minutes away from liftoff
所以现在离发射还差4分钟多一点
and Falcon 9 is moving into the final stages of the countdown.
而猎鹰9号已经进入到了倒计时的最后阶段
The first and second stages are nearly fully loaded with 1 million pound kerosene fuel and liquid oxygen.
一二级装满了接近453.6吨煤油燃料和液氧
It's a clear beautiful gorgeous day out there.
今天天气肥肠好
The first it's a clear beautiful gorgeous day out there.
(直播卡了)
the first stage should finish prop loading at t-minus three minutes
一级应该在倒计时3分钟装满燃料
and the second stage at t-minus two minutes as I mentioned earlier.
正如我前面说的 二级应该在倒计时2分钟装满燃料
Liquid oxygen is going to continue to top off up until the just before liftoff.
液氧将持续装满 直到快要起飞时
At t-minus 60 seconds be sure to listen for the call out that Falcon 9 is in startup
在倒计时60秒时 别忘了去听那个说猎鹰9号启动的呼号
that means that the Rockets autonomous internal flight computers have taken over the launch countdown.
这个呼号意味着火箭内部的自动飞行计算机接管了发射倒计时
The Starlink payload continues to be healthy.
有效载荷星链的状态持续良好
The Falcon 9 team is tracking no issues on the rocket.
猎鹰9号的团队目前没发现火箭有问题
Weather is looking really good and the range is green for launch.
天气看起来很好 发射区域畅通
So with all that let's just sit back and listen into the last few minutes of the countdown.
那么 在一切就绪的情况下 让我们坐下来放松一下 听着最后几分钟的倒计时
reddit.com/r/SpaceXLounge/comments/6jjpxk/spacex_callouts/
Stage 2 LOX load closeout.
二级火箭停止液氧加注
启动
猎鹰9号的飞控
接管了倒计时
Falcon 9 startup.
猎鹰9号启动
Oh please go for launch.
(发射指挥)允许发射
t-minus 30 seconds.
倒计时30秒
t-minus 15 seconds
倒计时15秒
10 9 8 7 6 5 4 3 2 1 0
速度          高度
二级遥测数据
Ignition, liftoff.
点火 起飞
起飞
猎鹰9号的固定夹具释放
飞行过程开始
Falcon 9's pitching downrange.
猎鹰9号程序转弯
Stage 1 propulsion is nominal.
一级火箭推力正常
Power and telemetry nominal.
动力 遥测信号正常
As you can see, Falcon 9 has had a successful liftoff from Pad 39A.
如你所见 猎鹰9号已从39A发射台成功起飞
Moments ago we throttle the engines down.
刚刚火箭的发动机节流了
Then will throttle back up.
之后会把油门加回来
Just in a second for preparation for Max-Q.
就是为了Max-Q做的准备
Max-Q stands for maximum aerodynamic pressure.
Max-Q的全称是最大气动压力
Falcon 9 supersonic.
猎鹰9号超音速
which is the highest stresses that the vehicle will see during ascent.
Max-Q是指火箭在上升段遇到的最大压力
Maximum aerodynamic pressure.
最大的气动压力
Max-Q
最大气动压力 - 这是火箭
(在上升段)受到的最大气动压力
Now coming up in about a minute we will have
three events happening back to back.
接下来一分钟内会连续发生三件事
First is main engine cutoff or MECO.
首先是一级发动机关机或者说MECO
This is where all nine M-1D engines will shut off to slow the vehicle down
这是指9台梅林1D发动机关闭来让火箭减速
in preparation for the second event which is stage separation.
为了分级 也就是第二件事
This is where the second stage will separate from the first stage
分级是指一二级分离
with stage one making its way back down to earth for landing
而一级会返回地球着陆
and stage two kicking off that third event that I mentioned
二级则开始进行我前面说的第三件事
which is SES-1
这就是SES-1
M-Vac engine chill.
真空梅林发动机预冷
Second engine startup one.
SES-1是指二级发动机第一次开机
This is where the M-Vac engine will light up
这是指真空梅林发动机将会点火
and propel the second stage along with the Starlink satellites to orbit.
并会推动二级还有星链卫星一起入轨
Expecting MECO to occur in about 30 seconds.
预计30秒内MECO会发生
MECO
一级发动机关机
MECO.
一级火箭发动机关机
分级
一级从二级上分离
Stage separation confirmed.
一二级分离确认
Successful MECO.
一级发动机成功关机
successful stage sep.
一二级成功分离
And it appears we have reignited or ignited that second stage engine for SES-1.
看起来二级火箭发动机也点火了 也就是SES-1
SES-1
二级发动机
第一次点火
Now we're just a few seconds from fairing deployed.
现在距离抛整流罩还差几秒钟
Again this fairing has flown before on a previous mission.
再说一下 这个整流罩是之前的任务中使用过的
Grid Fins are opening up.
栅格翼展开
抛整流罩
火箭顶部的保护性鼻锥
被抛离
Fairing separation.
整流罩分离
And we have fairing separation.
整流罩分离成功
We have successfully reuse this fairing
我们成功重复使用了这个整流罩
and now those halves and making their way back down to the sea.
现在这两半开始返回并准备溅落
where hopefully we can scoop them up.
我们希望能把它们擓(kuǎi)出来
So on the left side of your screen you have stage 1
屏幕左边是一级火箭
which it's making its way down to the drone ship.
它正在向下飞往无人船
And on the right you have stage 2 that M-Vac engine burning with 250,000 pounds of thrust.
而屏幕右边是有着934kN推力的真空梅林发动机
The grid fins appear to be fully deployed at this point.
现在 栅格翼已完全展开
Now while stage 2 continues on with the primary mission,
现在二级仍将继续进行主要任务
stage one's got its own plans.
但是一级有它自己的想法
It's going to execute 2 burns prior to landing.
它会在着陆前进行两次点火
The first is the entry burn.
首先是再入点火
That's where we will reignite three of the M-1D engines
这时它会重新点燃三个梅林1D发动机
which will help slow the stage down as it re-enters the upper part of the Earth's atmosphere.
会让一级火箭在再入地球高层大气时减速
Shortly thereafter we'll have a second burn
此后不久 会进行第二次点火
which we call the landing burn.
也称之为着陆点火
This is a single engine burn that brings the vehicle's velocity down rapidly
这是一个单发动机的点火 会让火箭的速度快速下降
in order to land safely on the drone ship.
这样才能安全地着陆在无人船上
At the same time during that burn
在着陆点火发生的同时
you'll see the landing legs will better currently fold it up along the side of the rocket
你会看到现在最好折叠起来放在火箭一侧的着陆腿
are going to deploy.
将会展开
M-Vac is looking good right now.
真空梅林发动机看起来状态不错
it looks a little overexposed on that image there.
右边的画面看起来有点儿过曝
but we can still see the pollutant coming out
但我们还是能看到污染物再往外排放
and we're still hearing good data.
同时 我们还能收到好的数据
So while we're two minutes away from entry burned.
那么 我们距离再入点火还差两分钟
Stage 2 nominal trajectory.
二级火箭轨道正常
Just a note on these Starlink satellites.
说明一下这些星链卫星
These 60 will be join in a constellation that's already on orbit.
这60颗卫星将会加入到已经入轨的星座
As we mentioned we've launched more than 360 satellites
正如之前所说 我们已经发射了超过360颗卫星
and again these are to provide high speed low latency internet to people down on that globe
再说一下  这些卫星是给地球上的人们提供高速低延迟的互联网
that you see on the right side of your screen.
在你的屏幕右边能看到地球
The M-Vac engine on stage 2 is that pool full power and on a nominal trajectory.
二级的真空梅林发动机在正常的轨道上开足马力
Now as stage 1 is making its way down.
与此同时一级正在下降
Again there are no engines burning while it's doing this.
一级下降过程中并没有发动机点火
It's basically coasting using the grid fins to steer
它只是用格栅翼控制姿态并滑行
and you can see those white puffs occasionally.
你有时能看到那些白色的气体
That's cold nitrogen gas
那是冷氮气
that is being used for attitude control part of our ACS system or attitude control system.
是姿态控制系统 也称ACS的一部分
okay that entry burn should be coming up here in about 15 seconds.
再入点火还差15秒
Meanwhile stage two continues on as planned.
与此同时二级继续按计划进行
一级火箭再入
一级火箭开始它的再入点火
减速进入大气层
Stage 1 entry burn startup.
一级再入点火开始
reddit.com/r/spacex/comments/2swnth/how_well_does_the_fts_work_on_an_empty_or_nearly/
Stage 1 FTS(flight termination system) safe.
一级FTS(飞行终止系统)良好
Was burnt for about 20 seconds.
点火了差不多20秒
For engines burning it once,
一次点火(这么多时间)
Stage 2 continues following nominal trajectory.
二级轨道持续正常
Stage 1 entry burn shut down.
一级再入点火关机
All right successful shutdown of that entry burn.
好吧 再入点火正常关机
Meanwhile stage two is looking great.
与此同时二级看起来没问题
All right full-screen shine here.
这个镜头亮瞎眼啊
There we go.
这个就正常多了
Now this burn on stage 2 is going to continue up until you hear the call out of SECO-1
二级的点火将会持续到SECO-1的呼号
or second engine cutoff one.
或者说是二级发动机一次关机
You're going to hear that pretty quickly after landing.
会在着陆之后很快听到这个呼号
Stage one entry trans-sonic.
一级火箭速度减至亚音速
M-Vac D beginning to throttle down.
真空梅林开始节流
Getting ready for that second engine cutoff.
二级发动机准备关机
Stage one landing burn startup.
一级着陆点火开始
Entering terminal guidance.
进入末端制导
Alright that landing burn is started.
好吧 着陆点火开始
Let's see if we can see the plume in the view
from the drone ship.
我们看看能不能在无人船上看到烟雾
一级火箭着陆
一级火箭开始它的着陆点火
减速并于海上(无人船)着陆
Stage one landing leg deploy.
一级火箭着陆腿展开
Stage 2 FDS(flight dynamics system) safe.
二级火箭FDS(飞行动力系统)良好
There it is.
它来了
Let's see.
让我们看看
We have cheers.
我们听到了欢呼声
We have a rocket.
我们看到了火箭
Awesome. This is the fourth landing for this booster.
很好 这是这枚一级火箭的第四次着陆
SECO-1
二级发动机第一次关机
And as you can hear everybody here is super dope too.
你能听到在场的各位都很高兴
You see it there.
你看它就在那儿
It's great.
这很好
It's a gorgeous day.
今天如此绚烂
Gorgeous rocket.
火箭如此绚丽
Alright.
好吧
And we have second engine cutoff on stage 2.
二级火箭发动机关机
And we are in a good orbit as well.
二级也处在正常的轨道上
Nominal orbit insertion.
轨道注入正常
So now stage two is going to coast in this orbit for a few minutes.
那么现在 二级会在这个轨道上滑行几分钟
and during this time the stage will actually start to spin around a central axis
在这段时间 二级会开始滚转
which gives the Starlink satellites the momentum
会给星链卫星一个动量
that they need in order to space themselves out over time after they deploy.
使得他们在部署后可以散开
We're going to take a quick break and come back here at t plus 14 minute.
我们会短暂地休息一下 在发射后14分钟回来
背景音乐：Cities in Flight - Test Shot Starfish
[Music]
[音乐]
Welcome back to the webcast for Starlink.
欢迎回到星链的发射直播
So far we have had a successful mission.
到目前为止 我们的任务都是成功的
And thus far we've had it at stage one ascent and landing.
到目前为止 以及火箭的上升段和着陆段都是成功的
And stage two got the Starlink satellites into a good orbit
二级也把星链卫星送入了正确的轨道
and is now coasting and getting ready for deployment of those Starlink satellites.
现在在滑行 并准备部署这些星链卫星
So we're gonna listen in for the callout it should come in about 30 seconds or so.
我们会在30秒左右的时间后听到这个呼号
We won't be able to see that right at that moment.
那时我们可能没法看到它们
We'll cut to the shot of the satellites deploying a little bit later.
我们会在卫星部署后的一小段时间内切到那个镜头
But about 20 seconds we should hear the callout.
但是20秒后我们就应该能听到呼号了
Payload deployed confirmed.
有效载荷部署确认
Okay we just heard the callout for payload deploy.
我们刚才听到了有效载荷部署的呼号
Now as the satellites begin to separate,
现在 当卫星开始分离时
over time they're going to open up their solar array
一段时间过去后它们会展开太阳能电池帆板
and over the next
而在接下来的
Oh there they go.
哦 它们这就分离了
All right that's those 60 Starlink satellites.
好吧 这就是那60颗星链卫星
Now shortly after as I was saying.
在我刚说完话不久
after just coming up in the next you know a few hours or so,
在接下来的几个小时内会发生
we're gonna see the solar arrays deploy.
我们会看到太阳能电池帆板展开
And over the next days and weeks the satellites will begin to distance themselves away from one another.
在未来的几天或者几周里卫星会四散开来
And use their on-board ion thrusters to make their way to their operational orbit of 550 kilometers.
并用它们的星载离子推进器让它们到达550km的运营轨道
Sorry that image is just always so beautiful.
画面总是那么美
and catches on me each time.
每次让我分心说错话
Now with that it brings our webcast to a close.
既然如此 我们的直播就到此结束了
We'd like to thank the 45th Space Wing.
我们感谢第45太空联队
For providing Range Safety today.
今天提供的范围控制
And the FAA for licensing today's launch.
还有美国联邦航空局对今天发射的许可
You can follow our website and social media platforms for updates on our next missions and milestones.
你可以跟进我们的网站和社交平台
来查看接下来的任务和里程碑的更新
So until next time be well and we'll see you next launch.
那么祝你一切顺利 欢迎你观看下次发射
背景音乐：Rollout - Test Shot Starfish
[Music]
[音乐]